<resources>
    <string name="app_name">First Year NITK</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="the_national_institute_of_technology_karnataka_nitk_surathkal_has_established_itself_as_one_of_the_top_technological_institutions_in_india_and_richly_deserved_recognition_as_an_institute_of_national_importance_under_the_nit_act_2007_accreditation_of_all_our_academic_programs_by_nba_many_with_highest_rating_recognition_as_a_qip_center_initiation_and_operationalization_of_mous_with_several_national_and_international_institutions_more_competitive_student_admissions_and_improved_performance_of_students_in_examinations_are_achievements_that_bear_testimony_to_our_commitment_to_maintain_quality_in_all_processes_and_systems_nitk_is_making_sustained_efforts_towards_consolidation_of_the_state_of_the_art_infrastructural_facilities_for_teaching_and_research_attracting_highly_qualified_and_motivated_staff_into_the_existing_pool_and_ensuring_availability_of_all_other_amenities_necessary_for_imparting_globally_relevant_technological_education_a_research_culture_is_taking_shape_in_the_institute_through_enhanced_r_d_activities_creation_of_centers_for_interdisciplinary_research_establishment_of_industry_sponsored_charis_stronger_interface_with_industry_alumni_and_a_special_focus_on_new_post_graduate_and_doctoral_programs_team_nitk_is_fully_geared_to_take_on_the_challenges_of_the_21st_century_to_establish_itself_as_a_world_class_technological_institution_prof_swapan_bhattacharya_director_nitk_surathkal"><![CDATA[The National Institute of Technology Karnataka (NITK), Surathkal has established itself as one of the top technological institutions in India and richly deserved recognition as an Institute of National Importance under the NIT Act 2007. Accreditation of all our academic programs by NBA; many with highest rating, recognition as a QIP Center, initiation and operationalization of MoUs with several national and international institutions, more competitive student admissions and improved performance of students in examinations are achievements that bear testimony to our commitment to maintain quality in all processes and systems. NITK is making sustained efforts towards consolidation of the state-of-the-art infrastructural facilities for teaching and research, attracting highly qualified and motivated staff into the existing pool and ensuring availability of all other amenities necessary for imparting globally relevant technological education. A research culture is taking shape in the institute through enhanced R & D activities, creation of centers for interdisciplinary research, establishment of industry-sponsored Charis, stronger interface with industry, alumni and a special focus on new post-graduate and doctoral programs. Team NITK is fully geared to take on the challenges of the 21st century to establish itself as a World-Class Technological Institution. -Prof. Swapan Bhattacharya, Director, NITK Surathkal.]]></string>
    <string name="vision">Vision</string>
    <string name="to_facilitate_transformation_of_students_into_good_human_beings_responsible_citizens_and_competent_professionals_focusing_on_assimilation_generation_and_dissemination_of_knowledge">To facilitate transformation of students into good human beings, responsible citizens and competent professionals, focusing on assimilation, generation and dissemination of knowledge.</string>
    <string name="missions">Missions</string>
    <string name="_1_impart_quality_education_to_meet_the_needs_of_profession_and_sociey_and_achieve_excellence_in_teaching_learning_and_research_2_attract_and_develop_talented_and_committed_human_resource_and_provide_an_environment_conducive_to_innovation_creativity_team_spirit_and_entrepreneurial_leadership_3_facilitate_effective_interactions_among_faculty_and_students_and_foster_networking_with_alumni_industries_institutions_and_other_stake_holders_4_practice_and_promote_high_standards_of_professional_ethics_transparency_and_accountability">1. Impart quality education to meet the needs of profession and sociey, and achieve excellence in teaching-learning and research. 2. Attract and develop talented and committed human resource, and provide an environment conducive to innovation, creativity, team-spirit and entrepreneurial leadership. 3. Facilitate effective interactions among faculty and students, and foster networking with alumni, industries, institutions and other stake-holders. 4. Practice and promote high standards of professional ethics, transparency and accountability.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="line">1.) The Rotaract Club conducts social, cultural and technical events for the students and club members alike. These include blood donation camps, cloth donation drives, coastal clean-up camps, and events conducted by the National Service Scheme (NSS) chapter of NITK. The Mangalore chapter of the Society for Promotion of Indian Classical Music and Culture Among Youth (SPICMACAY) is centred at NITK and is one of the biggest chapters in the country. It organises concerts and lectures by maestros of Indian classical art forms and strives to raise awareness of Indian culture in the surrounding regions through lectures, orientations and conventions. The chapter celebrated its Silver Jubilee by hosting the 27th Annual National Convention of SPICMACAY from 28 May to 3 June 2012. Literary, Stage and Debating Society (LSD) is the apex literary forum of the institute. The club mainly conducts quizzes while also holding debates and organising plays. LSD was formed in 2004 from the quiz club to cater to literary events other than quizzes. LSD is one of the best quiz clubs in India, having produced quizzers who have won competitions nationwide. Members of the club also contribute to the NITK Quiz blog, which has been active since 2008. Dance Dramatics and Fashion Club (DDFC) organises \'Spandan\' annually, which provides students a platform to showcase their talent at dance and theatre. The NITK Music Club organises music shows generally called Musical Night and play popular music at the outdoor auditoriums. A variety of styles are on display at these events, from Indian classical music to fusion to rock. The NITK Films Club screens movies at the Student\'s Activity Centre every Friday during the semester. Apart from English and Hindi releases, regional films are shown as well. The Press Club brings out a fortnightly wall magazine News Wagon, providing a tongue-in-cheek look at life around the campus, besides bringing out the official yearbook, The Vitruvian. VOICE (Vedic Oasis for Inspiration, Culture and Education) is a youth group run by the students, for the students. Using the principles present in the ancient Vedic scriptures, they train students in a blend of character and competence. The NITK Photography Club captures photos and videos of events happening at NITK. It conducts</string>
</resources>
